NGUYỄN BÁ HƯNG

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Contact

HCM, Vietnam

+84 869 052 629

bahung1221.github.io

bahung1221@gmail.com

bahung1221

Skills

FE - HTML, CSS, JS, VueJS, Tailwind

BE - NodeJS

BE - PHP

....

BE - Golang

• • • • •

Databases - MySQL, MongoDB

DevOps - Unix/Linux, Server Management

DevOps - Git, SSH, Docker, GoCD

Mobile - Flutter

.

Soft skill - Task management, Collaboration,

Problem Solving

.

Other - UX Design, User-oriented thinking

Languages

English (reading, writing, listening)

.

English (speaking)

• • • • •



About Me

5 years of experience in the software industry, with nearly 4 years in the Fullstack Developer role (FE Heavy).

Currently working on a small outsourcing startup, so I have the chance to work on all aspects of production-grade products.

I'm also a member of Grokking VN, which is a place for passionate developers to share and learn the deep and fundamental things in the software industry.

My pros are research and self-learning skills, with passion and curiosity about new things in the software industry.

My target is to become a Software Architect in the near future.



Education



Bachelor in University of Science, VNUHCM

09/2015 - 09/2018

Information Technology

Work Experience

SaigonTek 12/2019 - Present

Fullstack Developer / Solution Architect

- Developed 4+ products for VN & JP customers, mostly for the JP market.
- Worked on all aspects of the development processes: Requirement analytics, Planning, Wireframe review, Task Management, Development, and Monitoring.
- Contributed to some OSS projects on Github: shopify/draggable, conwnet/github1s,...
- Tech Stack: VueJS (Nuxt), Tailwindcss, NodeJS, PHP, MySQL, Linux cloud servers, AWS (EC2, ALB, S3, VPC, SG, SES), GoCD, Flutter (Android / iOS).

Gogojungle VN 12/2017 - 12/2019

Junior Fullstack Developer

- · Developed & maintained an e-commerce system for the Japanese market.
- Worked on all three Frontend, Backend & DevOps
- Tech Stack: VueJS, PHP (Laravel), NodeJS, MySQL, Linux cloud servers.

Certificates

UX Design Fundamental - Nordic

06/2021 - 08/2021

· Learned the UX design process and corresponding methods for a user-oriented product: Empathy, Define, Ideate, and Prototype.